Steven Hirschburger

987 Sixth Street, Jonesboro, AR 72405 ahirschb@youremail.com (870) 123-4567

Efficient, hard-working grocery store cashier with over 12 years' experience creating smooth customer experiences, processing payments and mentoring co-workers. Flexible and motivated to take on increasing levels of responsibility with little or no supervision. Committed to building an upbeat, safe environment with every interaction.

Key Skills

- Customer service
- ♦ Time management
- ♦ Multi-tasking
- ♦ Teamwork
- Accurate transaction handling

Professional Experience

Senior Grocery Clerk

Harps Food Stores, Jonesboro, AR j July 2016 - Present

- Greeting customers, executing transactions and fulfilling online and special-order requests
- ♦ Maintaining 100% accuracy in transactions
- Receiving 90% average customer satisfaction rating, 10% higher than store average
- Arranging and stocking department displays
- Training six entry-level grocery clerks
- Adept with cash register scanners and inventory software

Grocery Cashier

Kroger Stores, Memphis, TN / March 2012 - May 2016

- Greeted customers and processed payment transactions
- Handled special requests and complaints at Customer Service desk in-person and by phone
- Increased store loyalty card registrations by 15%, surpassing the company average of 10%
- Awarded Employee of the Month 10 times; received no customer complaints

Grocery Clerk

Emilio's Grocery, Memphis, TN / July 2006 - February 2012

- Greeted customersand processed payment transactions
- Bagged customers' groceries according to best practices to avoid damage
- Balanced average of \$1,000 cash drawer on each shift with no discrepancies
- Assisted with stocking shelves, setting up displays and cleaning floors

Education

High School Diploma

High School, West Memphis, AR, June 2008